<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GridFlare</string>
    <string name="launch_test">Launch a test</string>
    <string name="what_is_this">What is this ?</string>
    <string name="ping">
        <b>Ping:</b>\n
        Ping is a computer network administration software utility used to test the reachability of a host on an Internet Protocol (IP) network. It is available for virtually all operating systems that have networking capability, including most embedded network administration software.
        Ping measures the round-trip-time for messages sent from the originating host to a destination computer that are echoed back to the source.
        The round-trip-time is the sum of the time taken by the data to travel from the source to the destination and from the destination to the source.
        \n
        \n
        <b>Wi-Fi strength:</b>\n
        The Wi-Fi strength is the power of the received Wi-Fi wave from  your phone. This four-level (from 0 to 3) indicator is also represented on the top of your screen (the Wi-Fi indicator).
        This parameter is important: the weaker the signal is, the more you could loose receiving/sending data.
        \n
        \n
        <b>Proportion of lost packets:</b>\n
        This parameter shows the percentage of data packets that have been lost during the tests. Even if this is not a precious
        test, it can show the empirical probability of lost data packets during your utilisation of the network.
    </string>
    <string name="link_ping"><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ping_%28networking_utility%29">More information about Ping</a></string>
    <string name="working">Working</string>
    <string name="heatmap">HeatMap</string>
    <string name="scanner">Scanner</string>
    <string name="gridflare">GridFlare</string>
    <string name="historic">historic</string>
    <string name="save_data">Save Data</string>
    <string name="strength">Strength</string>
    <string name="ping_2">Ping</string>
    <string name="lost">Proportion of lost packets</string>
    <string name="time">Time for up</string>
    <string name="number_of_tests">number of tests</string>
    <string name="number_scan">Number of scans for this room:</string>
    <string name="create_new_place_rooms">Create new place/rooms</string>
    <string name="start_new_global_scan">Start new global scan</string>
    <string-array name="spinner_items">
        <item>Select a Room</item>
        <item>living room</item>
        <item>office</item>
        <item>kitchen</item>
        <item>bathroom</item>
        <item>bedroom 1</item>
        <item>bedroom 2</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
